

Fawad Naeem

Software Engineer

I have 1.5 years of experience in the Software Engineering domain ranging from web development to full-stack application development. I am passionate about learning new things, researching state-of-the-art tools, techniques, incorporating them in Full-Stack development. I am team player with а communication skills and a problem solver with a strong work ethic. Always open to constructive feedback for continuous improvement with a continuous learning mindset.

Contact Info

+92 3144016013

fawaddev@outlook.com

fawad4bros.github.io

Education

Institute of Southern Punjab Multan

Bachelor of Science Computer Science 2016 - 2021

Skills

Python Git

JavaScript Linux

Node.js Express.js

Angular Angular Material UI

SQL MongoDB

Soft Skills

Communication

Teamwork

Critical Thinking

Learning Aptitude

Work Experience

Trainee Software Engineer 8 months

Systems Limited OCT 2021 - MAY 2022

Wrote clear, clean code for various projects. Created interactive websites using MEAN stack and deployed. Collaborated effectively with members of software development team and personnel in CADM department.

Python Developer 4 months

Axiom World JUN 2021 - SEP 2021

Collaborated with quality assurance team to verify correct implementation of software development changes. Translated business requirements into logical and physical file structure designs. Applied change control best practices for software enhancements to minimize end-user disruptions.

